Hey everybody, head coach Matt LaFleur
[music] joins us from the league
meetings. And Matt, what's it like to
have your brother Mike here as a fellow
head coach? It's pretty surreal. [music]
It's pretty It's a pretty cool
experience. Um
I'm looking forward to being around him
and some of the other coaches and uh
make sure we
uh give him a hard time once we get all
get together.
Back home, a number of changes on your
coaching staff. Jonathan Gannon, your
new defensive coordinator. [music]
When he was hired, there was a lot of
talk. Is he a 4-3 guy? Is he a 3-4 guy?
In today's game, Matt, does it really
matter? Uh I don't think it does. I
think it's about our players and trying
to put them in the best position
possible. I think, you know, Hafley was
a four-down guy and we got to a bunch of
3-4 type principles in our base defense.
I mean, the majority of the game
nowadays is played with your nickel
defense out there, which is primarily a
four-man front. But, you know, then
again, you can get into odd spacing and
some of those 3-4 structures out of
nickel defense. So, I think I would say
it's fluid in [music] terms of,
you know, how we're going to build this
thing.
Jordan Morgan, is he ready to take over
at the hot corner full-time? Yeah, I
think so. I think last year and
everybody gets sick of me saying it, but
we're trying to get the best five out
there and we thought for our team, it
was best with to go with Sheed and
putting him at guard. But, it wasn't
necessarily as they were competing
[music] for that spot, we would have
been perfectly comfortable with Jordan
at left tackle. It's just
trying to find the best five that fit
together. Your past couple months,
you've had a chance to
go through the cut-ups, look back at
last season. What are you [music] taking
away? What are you gleaning from that?
Well, I think there was a lot of
opportunity there that we didn't
capitalize on and I think that's got to
be the mindset coming in as we got to
figure out ways to finish games and just
be productive in those critical moments.
I think when you look at it, it's kind
of bizarre, but like
three games where we don't punt on
offense
and we lose all three of those games.
Like, that can't happen and we got to be
better and it starts with us as coaches
and then ultimately our players got to
go out there and execute.
Couple of those players, Micah Parsons,
Tucker Kraft, big-time guys. How are
they progressing health-wise?
They're doing a great job. I think
they're they're both putting in the
work. They've attacked this thing with
the right mindset. I think our trainers
have done a hell of a job with them.
That'll be a huge boost for our football
team when we get those guys back and
they're healthy and ready to go.
Matt, have a good couple days. Thank
you. Thanks, Larry.